birthdayalarm.com 2006-10-17

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Our Commitment to You

We, at BirthdayAlarm, understand and respect that your privacy should always remain strictly under your control. It is because of this philosophy that you can be confident that the information you divulge to BirthdayAlarm will not be accessible to people whom you have not authorized. Neither will it be sold or otherwise distributed to third parties other than in accordance with this policy without your consent. BirthdayAlarm is not a source of unsolicited email.

Questions

1.| What personal details do you need to know?  
---|---  
2.| When is my information given out?  
3.| What do you use my personal details for?  
4.| Does BirthdayAlarm sell my information to third parties?  
5.| Will I be added to any mailing lists?  
6.| Do you send unsolicited emails?  
7.| What do you use cookies for?  
8.| How will I be notified of changes?  
9.| How do I cancel my membership?  
10.| How do I contact you?  
  
What personal details do you need to know?

The minimum of information we ask for BirthdayAlarm is your name, email address and date of birth.

We will not give out any information without your knowledge.

You may update this information at any time by simply clicking on the 'My Profile' button once you have signed in and then updating the details as you wish.

When is my information given out?

Your name, birthday (optionally including year of birth) and email address is made available to other members who you have agreed should be notified of your birthday.

What do you use my personal details for?

We will use your name so that we can personalise your experience with us. We will use your email address to contact you from time to time and we will use your email address for security reasons to confirm that you are who you say you are.

We also collect other data, which may include your IP address and what browser you are using. We use this information to statistically analyze site usage and to customize our site's content, layout and services. The resulting information will allow us to improve our site and better understand and serve our users. It is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis only.

Does BirthdayAlarm sell my information to third parties?

As a matter of policy, we do not sell, rent or lend any of your personal information to third parties other than in accordance with this policy without your consent. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personal information may be used in the normal routine to provide our range of services to you.

 **Service Management.** We use your personal information to provide the services you request. We use your personal information to: troubleshoot problems; measure consumer interest in our services, inform you about offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our Terms of Use; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.

You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. You may make changes to your email notification preferences at any time.

 **Internal Service Providers for Our Operations.** We may use third parties that we refer to as internal service providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of the business, product and service operations that we provide to you (e.g., search technology, email support) and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to these internal service providers. These internal service providers' are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information we provide them for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific outsourced BirthdayAlarm related operation, unless you have explicitly agreed or given your prior permission to them for additional uses.

In some instances, the internal service provider may collect information directly from you (such as for BirthdayAlarm surveys). In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the internal service provider, and all additional information you provide them and their additional uses will be strictly up to you. If you provide additional information to an internal service provider directly, then their use of your personal information is governed by their applicable privacy policy.

 **Advertisers.** We disclose non-personally identifiable aggregated (gather up data across all member accounts) information to advertisers and other third parties. An example of non-personally identifiable information would be 'the number of members aged 20-30'.

 **Law Enforcement.** BirthdayAlarm cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and the BirthdayAlarm service. Therefore, in response to a genuine request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can disclose personal information about you.Third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

 **Acquisition.** It is possible that as we continue to develop our website and our business, BirthdayAlarm's service and/or related assets might be acquired. Notwithstanding any provision in this policy to the contrary, in event of a merger or acquisition, your personal information may be transferred to the acquiring entity, and become subject to the acquirer's data practices.

Will I be added to any mailing lists?

We do not sell, rent or lend email addresses for any other purpose than in direct association with your use of the BirthdayAlarm service or as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

Do you send unsolicited emails?

BirthdayAlarm will not send any unsolicited information, including email. You will, however receive emails which form an essential part of the service.

What do you use cookies for?

Cookies are a standard internet technology, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their members. Cookies allow us to store and retrieve login information on a user's system. They provide us with data that we can use to improve our service to you. If you so choose, you can save your login or password so you don't have to re-enter them each time you visit our site.

Cookies themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our web site if you do so.

How will I be notified of changes?

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on the Site. All amended terms shall automatically be effective immediately after posting on the Site. We will notify you in accordance with your Notification Preferences.

How do I cancel my membership?

You always have the option not to become a member or to cancel your membership at any time.

If you are a member and no longer wish to participate in BirthdayAlarm you can sign in to the site and click on the 'My Profile' at the top of the page; then select 'cancel membership' and follow the simple instructions.

This action will cancel your membership and delete your details from the system. You will be assured that, BirthdayAlarm will not contact you directly at the email address we have on record for you, other than to respond to requests you may make to BirthdayAlarm in the future.

How do I contact you?

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website or your dealings with this website, you can contact us via the Contact Us page, or by writing to:

    | Customer Support  
---|---  
| Birthday Alarm, LLC.  
| 142 Tenth Street  
| San Francisco  
| CA 94103  
| USA
